export default data = [
  {
      question: "After hours of discussion, our class finally reached the _____ that we would go to Hualien for our graduation trip.",
      options: ["balance","conclusion","definition","harmony"],
      correct_option: "conclusion"
  },
  {
      question: "Jane _____ her teacher by passing the exam with a nearly perfect score; she almost failed the course last semester.",
      options: ["bored","amazed","charmed","informed"],
      correct_option: "amazed"
  },
  {
      question: "The vacuum cleaner is not working. Let’s send it back to the _____ to have it inspected and repaired.",
      options: ["lecturer","publisher","researcher","conclusion"],
      correct_option: "manufacturer"
  },
  {
      question: "Due to the global financial crisis, the country’s exports _____ by 40 percent last month, the largest drop since 2000.",
      options: ["flattered","transformed","relieved","decreased"],
      correct_option: "decreased"
  },
  {
      question: "The potato chips have been left uncovered on the table for such a long time that they no longer taste fresh and _____.",
      options: ["solid","crispy","original","smooth"],
      correct_option: "crispy"
  },
  {
      question: "The townspeople built a _____ in memory of the brave teacher who sacrificed her life to save her students from a burning bus.",
      options: ["monument","refugee","souvenir","firecracker"],
      correct_option: "monument"
  },
  {
      question: "The students in Professor Smith’s classical Chinese class are required to _____ poems by famous Chinese poets.",
      options: ["construct","expose","recite","install"],
      correct_option: "recite"
  },
  {
      question: "Although Mr. Tang claims that the house belongs to him, he has not offered any proof of _____.",
      options: ["convention","relationship","insurance","ownership"],
      correct_option: "ownership"
  },
  {
      question: "Ancient Athens, famous for its early development of the democratic system, is often said to be the _____ of democracy.",
      options: ["mission","target","cradle","milestone"],
      correct_option: "cradle"
  },
  {
      question: "The candy can no longer be sold because it was found to contain artificial ingredients far beyond the _____ level.",
      options: ["abundant","immense","permissible","descriptive"],
      correct_option: "permissible"
  },
  {
      question: "Jack’s excellent performance in last week’s game has _____ all the doubts about his ability to play on our school basketball team.",
      options: ["erased","canceled","overlooked","replaced"],
      correct_option: "erased"
  },
  {
      question: "It is bullying to _____ a foreign speaker’s accent. No one deserves to be laughed at for their pronunciation.",
      options: ["mock","sneak","prompt","glare"],
      correct_option: "mock"
  },
  {
      question: "Mary lost ten kilograms in three months, so her _____ skin-tight jeans are now hanging off her hips.",
      options: ["barely","evenly","currently","formerly"],
      correct_option: "formerly"
  },
  {
      question: "The police officer showed us pictures of drunk driving accidents to highlight the importance of staying _____ on the road.",
      options: ["sober","majestic","vigorous","noticeable"],
      correct_option: "sober"
  },
  {
      question: "The claim that eating chocolate can prevent heart disease is _____ because there is not enough scientific evidence to support it.",
      options: ["creative","disputable","circular","magnificent"],
      correct_option: "disputable"
  },
]